# Godworks C. Eric | SOFTWARE ENGINEER - IT RESEARCH PROFESSIONAL



Location: 10c Aganunu Street Mgbuoba, Port-Harcourt

Telephone: 08057556619, 09062108833

Email: ericgodworks@yahoo.com

Gender: Male DoB: 08/03/1991

Nationality/State/LGA: Nigerian / Rivers State / Emohua

Plans to Relocation: Yes

### **Profile:**

Software Engineer with over 8 years of experience in ERP Software, Networking, System maintenance, Decision support, digital communication and graphic designing. 3 years of experience in Radio Programming and music scheduling, utilising my expertise, I will be responsible for solving algorithmically complex problems, front-end and backend services that can scale to millions of requests and also globally delivering software with exceptional customer experience.

#### **Education:**

Degree Earned, Institution Name, Address, Start and End Date

B.Tech (Hons) Information Technology, Lovely Professional University, Phagwara, Jalandhar, India, 09/2010 to 08/2014. O'Level, Akpor Grammer School, Ozuoba, Port Harcourt, Rivers State, Nigeria, 09/2002 to 06/2007. FSLC, CSS Mabuodohia, Port Harcourt, Rivers State, Nigeria, 09/1995 to 07/2001.

## **Work History:**

Job Title, Organization, Address, Start and End Date (Mo/Year), Name of Supervisor, Duties, and accomplishments

**Librarian/IT Personnel**, Megalectrics LTD (Beatfm, Classicfm, Naijafm), 35 Tombia St, Rurome-Rezigbu 500272, Port-Harcourt, Rivers State, Nigeria, **11/2019 to date.** 

Supervisor: **Anieka Essien/Funbi/Spaceman**, Played a backdoor role in *making Beatfm, Classicfm, Naijafm the leading radio music stations* in Port-Harcourt, Nigeria. Creating goals, clocks, markers, sound codes, and schedules. I ensure shows and presenters have the right combination of songs to fit trends, time, agenda, playlist and needs.

Instructor, Loctech, Artillery Junction, Port-Harcourt, Rivers State, Nigeria, 12/2015 to 11/2017.

Coordinator - Java Programming. Instructor - Web Design, CMS, and Graphics designs. Instructor - Web Development.

Handled these classes and improved understanding of the concepts.

**Instrumentalist,** *Victory International Church, Enugu,* Nigeria, **03/2015-10/2015**, Supervisor: Past. David Oluwami Keyboardist and Bassist, producing rhymes using instruments. Improved quality of sound.

**Administrator**, *Dawille Cyber Café*, *UST back gate*, Rivers State, Nigeria, **03/2008 - 10/2008**. Attendant, Troubleshooter, Research Surfer. Improved Job description by 50%.

Administrator, Fon Micro Cyber Cafe, Rumuola Round-about, Rivers State, Nigeria, **05/2009 - 10/2009.**Attendant, Troubleshooter, Research Surfer, Improved Job description by 50%.

#### **Training and Professional Developments:**

Course Name, Venue (Institution, Address), Date

NYSC Cert., National Youth Service Corps, Enugu, Nigeria, 04/2014 to 10/2015.

Six Months course in Software Engineering (Two Semesters), Lovely Professional University, Jalandhar, India, 7/01/2014 – 24/07/2014.

Six Week on C#/ASP.Net, Bhai Gurdas Institute of Engineering and Technology, Sangrur (Pb.) India, 13/06/2010 – 25/07/2010.

**Six Week Summer Training in CCNA, Web Designing, and Network Security,** Bhai Gurdas Institute of Engineering and Technology, Sangrur (Pb.) India, **13/06/2010 – 25/07/2010.** 

Information Security and Digital Marketing, SRM University, Kattankulathur, India, 27/02/2010 – 28/02/2010. Industrial Training, Intellisence Technology, Jalandhar, India, 06/2013 – 08/2013.

Oracle Workforce Development Program, NIIT Jalandhar BMC Chowk Centre, India, 07/2013 – 10/2013. Computer Maintenance, Admas Computer, Ikwerre Road, Port-Harcourt, Nigeria, 04/2006 – 09/2006 Online Studies, Personal Computer, currently

### References available on request: